with Japan now in a dire situation prime
minister Suzuki would order cabinet
secretary sakam misu to discreetly
compose a study of Japan's last
remaining resources to see if there was
any hope of winning the war Gathering
both military and civilian experts from
across all vital Industries the sakuu
report would highlight the extent to
which Japan's economy was on the brink
of collapse with its findings being far
worse than anyone had imagined steel
production was less than 100,000 tons
per month 70% below the official
estimate along with the lack of coal
having cut the production of Munitions
in half a lack of resources had also cut
aircraft production to only 30% of
potential output with the entire
transportation system on the brink of
collapse due to fuel shortages and a
lack of Manpower as the sakom Mizu
report predicted in weeks there would be
no rail transportation between cities
construction of